Austin Taylor

VR/AR Developer

As a visionary one of my most compelling strengths lies on my ability to be a prolific thinker, with the means to create and use unique paths to reach my objectives. As an Information, Communication and Technology major at Florida State University, my ambition lies within searching for and testing new technologies. I specialize and have a deep passion for all interactive and immersive media.

Personal Info

Address

1885 Oakes Blvd, Naples, Fl

Phone

239-961-1656

E-mail

adt17d@my.fsu.edu

Date of birth

1996-04-03

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/austintaylor-705393129/

Skills

VR/AR Development

Verbal/Written Communication

Project Management

Software Testing & Debugging

Data analysis

Media Relations

C++, Java, Java script, HTLM5, CSS

Experience

2018-09 -

VR/AR Developer

present

Gocovalent

- Held a lead role in the development of a VR environment using Unreal Engine 4
- $\bullet\,$ for the Florida Disabled Outdoors Association.

Developed interactive games with limited mobility for our users as well as

• inserting 360-degree video "portals" for transportation.

Turned this immersive virtual reality experience into an engaging virtual reality

• application

3D modeled assets using Maya to import into UE4

2018-05 -

Developer Internship

2018-08

Parr Moto

- Held the lead role in programming an interactive eLearning course for 500 MasterCraft employees using Articulate/Storyline 360
- Assistant in writing a strategic brief with the means to develop a comprehensive sales training curriculum for all MasterCraft employees
- Assistant in building the developing that gained approval to move forward with this project
- Was granted the honor of having my module approved as the standard template for all future sales training courses.

2016-01 -

Owner

present

TAYTM'S L.L.C

- Distribute Automated Telling Machines throughout the state of Florida
- Provide full installation, maintenance and technical support
- Provide Data Analysis for Revenue Streams
- Enhanced operational efficiency and productivity by managing budgets, accounts and machine traffic

Software

Final Cut Pro

Dreamweaver

Articulate 360

Excellent

Unreal Engine 4

Visual Studio

Advanced

Blender

Advanced

Maya

2013-10 -2017-03

Digital Media Specialist

Entree Magazine

- Developed key messaging, branding and positioning statementS
- Drafted and managed print, online and social media communications designed to promote company brand, image and values
- Assistant and consultant to editor in chief for all content as well as layout coordination/design
- Ensure smooth operation for all digital tools and applications (e.g. website, blogs and social media)

Education

2015-06 -

Advanced

Excellent

Florida State University

2019-06

Bachelor of Science: Information, Communication and Technology